<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on Ampretia:Dev</title>
    <link>http://ampretia.co.uk/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on Ampretia:Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:14:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ampretia.co.uk/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Composer &amp;#8211; Logging</title>
      <link>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2018-06-08-hyperledger-composer-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2018-06-08-hyperledger-composer-logging/</guid>
      <description>Hyperledger Composer - Logging Many years ago there was an insect that caught in a relay. Time has moved on, but the successor to that insect still can make itself known! Logging though is more than about just finding the diagnostics to help squash the specific code bugs. It can be used to see operational performance issues, spot configuration mistakes, and gaining confidence in how the code is working.
How does Hyperledger Composer go about it&amp;rsquo;s logging then?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using custom dockerfiles for managing Hyperledger Composer Network Cards</title>
      <link>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2018-06-08-using-custom-dockerfiles-for-managing-hyperledger-composer-network-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2018-06-08-using-custom-dockerfiles-for-managing-hyperledger-composer-network-cards/</guid>
      <description>Using Docker to help access Composer Cloud Wallets Within a cloud application, eg a nodejs app pushed to Cloud Foundary (other clouds are available) to access a Composer Smart Contract running on Hyperledger Fabric,
then you need the ability to store the network cards in some location that&amp;rsquo;s not your laptop.
Using the &amp;lsquo;Cloud wallets&amp;rsquo; feature it&amp;rsquo;s quite easy to do this. You have the choice of S3, IBM Cloud Object Store, Cloudant, REDIS etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting outside-in with docker-compose[r] networks</title>
      <link>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2017-11-11-getting-outside-in-with-docker-composer-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 18:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ampretia.co.uk/post/2017-11-11-getting-outside-in-with-docker-composer-networks/</guid>
      <description>I had several docker containers spun up, all happily talking to each other on their own network. All happy for me to talk to them from the host Ubuntu system as well. Slight issue of when a configuration is exported from one of the docker containers, it was referring to the others by the domain it knew, example.com - not so great to use it from the host that knew it via localhost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
